<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Flogo CLI on Project Flogo - Docs and Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/flogo-cli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Flogo CLI on Project Flogo - Docs and Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/flogo-cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flogo CLI</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/flogo-cli/flogo-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/flogo-cli/flogo-cli/</guid>
      <description>The flogo CLI tool has a bunch of different actions and command. Below is a complete list of all of them, including samples on how to use them.
Commands create This command is used to create a flogo application project.
Create the base sample project with a specific name.
flogo create my_app  Create a flogo application project from an existing flogo application descriptor.
flogo create -f myapp.json  install This command is used to install a contribution to your project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flogogen CLI</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/flogo-cli/flogogen-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/flogo-cli/flogogen-cli/</guid>
      <description>The flogogen CLI tool has a bunch of different actions and command. Below is a complete list of all of them, including samples on how to use them. For a walk through of how to use these commands to create new extensions, check out the extension developer chapter.
Trigger With the trigger command of flogogen you can create a custom flogo trigger. To do so, run:
flogogen trigger mytrigger  Project Structure The create command creates a basic structure and files for an trigger.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>